<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://srioes.github.io</id>
    <title>SRIES|实验学校第二科研所</title>
    <updated>2020-04-18T05:02:38.301Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://srioes.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://srioes.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>温故而知新</subtitle>
    <logo>https://srioes.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://srioes.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, SRIES|实验学校第二科研所</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweet Dreams 第一部分]]></title>
        <id>https://srioes.github.io/post/sweet-dreams-di-yi-bu-fen/</id>
        <link href="https://srioes.github.io/post/sweet-dreams-di-yi-bu-fen/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-04-18T04:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>一个原创英文小说，改编自Minecraft知名整合包&quot;GTNH&quot;。</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>一个原创英文小说，改编自Minecraft知名整合包&quot;GTNH&quot;。</p>
<!-- more -->
<h1 id="sweet-dreams-part-1">Sweet Dreams Part 1</h1>
<p>Who am I?<br>
I’m Gregorius T.<br>
Where I am?<br>
Now I am in a new planet called GTNH, the natural environment here is greatly comfortable. Here are also animals, plants and the same science rules as the Earth, but I haven’t seen anybody so far. And...why I know these things?<br>
I am a realist. It’s necessary for me to throw away all the feelings in mind,because actions are always the most important things. Here’s no anybody doesn’t means there will be no anybody, go and take action.<br>
My first task will be to find food, and look for a suitable home for me. In my mind, the night will  have completely darkness. I run about three kilometers and pick some berries in a forest, then I collect some of fruits to be as dinner. There is a river nearby, the gravel by the river is very hard, so I decide to select a few flints as simple tools. Three hours goes by, the night is coming. I am still working, but suddenly feel something dangerous was probably moving close to me. I shout at the front with tons of fear, then run into the forest soon and put lots of branches and leaves to hide myself. All the things with colors can’t be seen because of completely darkness, I can only hear some strange sounds, like”waaaaa...broooo...” or  “sssss...”. I think these are probably my enemies but they can’t be beaten by my weak body.<br>
Later, I finally fall asleep in such a uncomfortable place. I believe I’ll be strong enough one day.</p>
<h3 id="written-by-ticl4">————written by TiCl4</h3>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>