<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://sries.lwzheng.icu</id>
    <title>SRIES|实验学校第二科研所</title>
    <updated>2020-04-21T06:07:48.119Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://sries.lwzheng.icu"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://sries.lwzheng.icu/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>温故而知新</subtitle>
    <logo>https://sries.lwzheng.icu/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://sries.lwzheng.icu/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, SRIES|实验学校第二科研所</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[谈一点对新裤子乐队的认识]]></title>
        <id>https://sries.lwzheng.icu/post/newpants1/</id>
        <link href="https://sries.lwzheng.icu/post/newpants1/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-04-18T13:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>新裤子乐队，一群不会变老的人</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>新裤子乐队，一群不会变老的人</p>
<!-- more -->
<p>（偷偷吐槽下网易云没有新裤子的版权）</p>
<hr>
<p>蟹腰，人在飞机，刚下中国。</p>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>
<h1 id="开始听新裤子的歌">开始听新裤子的歌</h1>
</li>
<li>
<h2 id="乐夏"><strong>乐夏</strong></h2>
</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="https://i.loli.net/2020/04/04/mwEBglz4oLVrqye.jpg" alt="乐队的夏天新裤子" loading="lazy"><br>
初次认识新裤子乐队，是在2019年夏天的一档节目《乐队的夏天》（以下简称乐夏）。摇滚乐我小时候就在听，听的是许巍、郑钧、黑豹、唐朝。只不过中间有中断过一大段时间（一直到乐夏之后），中间听的是电音和民谣。</p>
<p>起初，《乐夏》里我最想听的不是新裤子（听都没听过），也不是老牌摇滚面孔，而是鹿先森这种偏流行化的乐队。在补完乐夏之后的一段时间之后，我突然去回味了一下各个乐队的歌，其中包括新裤子乐队。我突然觉得新裤子的几首歌《别再问我什么是disco》，《你要跳舞吗》，《生命因你而火热》和《没有理想的人不伤心》非常好听，于是我打算深入听一下新裤子的歌。</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h2 id="深入听歌"><strong>深入听歌</strong></h2>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<h3 id="土摇本土摇滚">土摇（本土摇滚）</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>从《生命因你而火热》和《没有理想的人不伤心》入手，我开始听了几首同样风格的歌，包括《假如生活欺骗了你》《弹着吉他的少年》等等。确实有点味，也很好听，于是决定再继续听听。<br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2020/04/04/w2RFnQo6P3fJ5is.jpg" alt="专辑《生命因你而火热》" loading="lazy"></p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3 id="新浪潮new-wave">新浪潮（New Wave）</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>按时间顺序往后听，就是新浪潮风格的音乐了。新浪潮有点像电子音乐的风格，而我之前恰好喜欢听电音，这种风格我自然爱听，</p>
<p>暂时先写到这。。。——笔者exWatermelon</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweet Dreams 第一部分]]></title>
        <id>https://sries.lwzheng.icu/post/sweetdreams1/</id>
        <link href="https://sries.lwzheng.icu/post/sweetdreams1/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-04-18T04:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>一个原创英文小说，改编自Minecraft知名整合包&quot;GTNH&quot;。</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>一个原创英文小说，改编自Minecraft知名整合包&quot;GTNH&quot;。</p>
<!-- more -->
<h1 id="sweet-dreams">Sweet Dreams</h1>
<h2 id="part-1-the-first-day">Part 1 The First Day</h2>
<pre><code>  Who am I?
  I’m GregoriusT.
  Where I am?
  I think that I am in a new planet, called GTNH. The natural environment here is greatly comfortable. Here are also animals, plants and the same science rules as the Earth, but I haven’t seen anybody so far. And...why I know these things?
  I am a realist. It’s necessary for me to throw away all the feelings in mind,because actions are always the most important things. Here’s no anybody doesn’t means there will be no anybody, go and take action.
  My first task will be to find food, and look for a suitable home to live. In my mind, the night will  have complete darkness. I run about three kilometers and pick some berries in a forest, then collect some of fruits to be as dinner. There is a river nearby, the gravel by the river is always hard, so I decide to select a few flints as simple tools. Three hours goes by, the night is coming. I am still working, but suddenly feel something dangerous is probably moving close to me. I shout at the front with tons of fear, then run into the forest soon and put lots of branches and leaves to hide myself. All the things with colors can’t be seen because of darkness, I can only hear some strange sounds outside, like”waaaaa...wroooo...” or  “sssss...”. Who are they? Are they my enemies? I don’t know.
  Later, I finally fall asleep in such an uncomfortable place. I can have a sweet dream.
                                                ————written by TiCl4
</code></pre>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>